

FEDERICO Barbieri

Federico has a background in advertising, is currently studying Multimedia Design, and works as a Frontend Developer. With a unique blend of creative and technical skills, he is able to create engaging digital experiences that resonate with audiences. He is passionate about staying up-to-date with emerging trends and technologies, and is committed to delivering top-notch work that meets its clients' needs.

• Copenhagen V

+45 52 22 19 89

federico.pedro.barbieri@gmail.com

(im) www.linkedin.com/in/fedebarbieri

EDUCATION

2022-2024

Multimedia Design @ KEA

2012-2013

Copywriting @ Brother

2011-2013

Advertising @ ESCP

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 -

Frontend Developer @ Aim Robotics

2020 -

Freelance Copywriter

2017 - 2020

Senior Creative @ City of Buenos Aires

2016 - 2017

Creative @ DDB Argentina

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma
- WordPress
- Elementor